<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salesforce Tek Talks</title>
    <link>https://gminero.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Salesforce Tek Talks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 10:34:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gminero.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Blog Journey</title>
      <link>https://gminero.github.io/posts/my-blog-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 10:34:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gminero.github.io/posts/my-blog-journey/</guid>
      <description>2 Years ago I decided to start a personal blog to write about tech subjects (mostly salesforce related), In this post, I will take you through the journey that lead to what my blog is today.
The Beggining 2 Years ago, I wanted to begin blogging about Salesforce subjects. I had recently discovered Heroku and was already familiar with Django. So for me it was a no brainer, Start a blog, use Django, Heroku and Voila&amp;hellip; Create content!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://gminero.github.io/about/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 15:52:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gminero.github.io/about/about-me/</guid>
      <description>For 2 years, I was a Product Specialist for the Coveo for Salesforce line of business. This included troubleshooting visualforce pages, lightning communities, lightning components, apex code as well as Coveo related components. I then transitioned to becoming Coveo for Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Technical Evangelist where I focused on assisting to develop and support the growing community in the Salesforce environment.
Today, I dedicate most of my time to helping our partners in our growing community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lwc Aura Wrappers</title>
      <link>https://gminero.github.io/posts/lwc-aura-wrappers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 10:52:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gminero.github.io/posts/lwc-aura-wrappers/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we will create an Aura wrapper component around a LWC that fires an APP event to an external Aura component. Wrapping your LWC will help you communicate with other aura components that cannot or have not been migrated to LWC.
Getting Started You will need to get yourself setup with Salesforce-DX, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to do so, this is a good time to get your environemnt setup since we will use it to deploy our LWC to a scratch org for testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightning Web Component Community Case Creation</title>
      <link>https://gminero.github.io/posts/lightning-web-component-community-case-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 13:52:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gminero.github.io/posts/lightning-web-component-community-case-creation/</guid>
      <description>In this post we will create a case creation form, using the lightning-record-edit-form component alongise proper redirection to the record page once the button has been submitted.
Getting Started You will need to get yourself setup with Salesforce-DX, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to do so, this is a good time to get your environemnt setup since we will use it to deploy our LWC to a scratch org for testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Deflection from A-Z</title>
      <link>https://gminero.github.io/speaker-sessions/case-deflection-from-a-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 16:40:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gminero.github.io/speaker-sessions/case-deflection-from-a-z/</guid>
      <description>French Touch Dreamin 2019 Case Deflection from A-Z
During this speaker session I did an overview of customizing a complete Contact Support Form alongside a Custom Deflection component in Lightning Communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free AI Powered Search for Lightning Communities</title>
      <link>https://gminero.github.io/speaker-sessions/free-ai-powered-search-for-lightning-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 16:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gminero.github.io/speaker-sessions/free-ai-powered-search-for-lightning-communities/</guid>
      <description>Dream Olé 2017   During this speaker session I introduced Coveo&amp;rsquo;s Free offering which is available since 2017.
The package is available as a free Appexchange package in which you can get started farily quickly.
Coveo Free Version
Getting Started with Coveo for Salesforce Free Edition</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>